{
  "openingRemarks": "NB: to indicate that an answer is a repeating decimal expansion, let the repeating part occur more than once, and let the answer end with 2 or more dots.<br>E.g. 13/2 can be entered as 6.5000..",
  "extraDescription": "for numbers in 1-25",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "23 &times; 3",
      "answer": "69",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5555...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{7}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.714285714285...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{7}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.285714285714...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.16666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &times; 2",
      "answer": "40",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{7}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.142857142857...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "19 &times; 4",
      "answer": "76",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{5}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{8}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.6666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "16 &times; 3",
      "answer": "48",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "4&sup2;",
      "answer": "16",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 6 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "6,0,3,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "16 &times; 4",
      "answer": "64",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 &times; 3",
      "answer": "63",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 24 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "24,0,12,2,8,3,6,4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1&sup3;",
      "answer": "1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; 5",
      "answer": "65",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "17 &times; 5",
      "answer": "85",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "16 &times; 2",
      "answer": "32",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{6}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.6666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{6}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.16666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.363636...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{6}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 20 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "20,0,10,2,5,4"
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &times; 4",
      "answer": "80",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.4444...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "24 &times; 3",
      "answer": "72",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "7&sup2;",
      "answer": "49",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{16}\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &times; 4",
      "answer": "56",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "5&sup2;",
      "answer": "25",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{6}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.545454...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; 7",
      "answer": "91",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 13 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "13,0,13,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "16 &times; 5",
      "answer": "80",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "24 &times; 2",
      "answer": "48",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 18 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "18,0,9,2,6,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{8}\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 &times; 2",
      "answer": "42",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 5 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "5,0,5,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{7}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.875",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{6}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.3333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 16 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "16,0,8,2,4,4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 12 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "12,0,6,2,4,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.083333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{1}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{8}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{7}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.428571428571...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 17 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "17,0,17,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "22 &times; 2",
      "answer": "44",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "17 &times; 3",
      "answer": "51",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.416666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1&sup2;",
      "answer": "1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{9}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "25 &times; 3",
      "answer": "75",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{6}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.83333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.375",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &times; 5",
      "answer": "100",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "10&sup2;",
      "answer": "100",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &times; 2",
      "answer": "36",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "22 &times; 4",
      "answer": "88",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &times; 3",
      "answer": "60",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{9}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{7}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &times; 3",
      "answer": "42",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{8}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.727272...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &times; 7",
      "answer": "98",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{5}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; 3",
      "answer": "39",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{1}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &times; 3",
      "answer": "54",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 10 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "10,0,5,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{4}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{6}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.6666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 3 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "3,0,3,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.090909...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &times; 5",
      "answer": "70",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; 4",
      "answer": "52",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; 2",
      "answer": "26",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &times; 4",
      "answer": "60",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "23 &times; 2",
      "answer": "46",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &times; 5",
      "answer": "90",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{6}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6&sup2;",
      "answer": "36",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &times; 2",
      "answer": "28",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 14 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "14,0,7,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "3&sup3;",
      "answer": "27",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 21 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "21,0,7,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{9}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.818181...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "24 &times; 4",
      "answer": "96",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.181818...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{10}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.83333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 11 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "11,0,11,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "25 &times; 4",
      "answer": "100",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{6}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.75",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 23 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "23,0,23,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.1111...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "19 &times; 2",
      "answer": "38",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "2&sup3;",
      "answer": "8",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.3333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "25 &times; 2",
      "answer": "50",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &times; 4",
      "answer": "72",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{7}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.583333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &times; 5",
      "answer": "75",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 7 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "7,0,7,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &times; 6",
      "answer": "90",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 19 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "19,0,19,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "9&sup2;",
      "answer": "81",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 2 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "2,0,2,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.3333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{11}{12}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.916666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{8}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.8888...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 1 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "1,0,1,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "19 &times; 3",
      "answer": "57",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.454545...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 &times; 6",
      "answer": "84",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.2222...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{9}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.272727...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "23 &times; 4",
      "answer": "92",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "17 &times; 4",
      "answer": "68",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{8}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 22 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "22,0,11,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "2&sup2;",
      "answer": "4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{7}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.636363...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 9 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "9,0,3,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.3333...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{6}{7}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.857142857142...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "22 &times; 3",
      "answer": "66",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 25 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "25,0,5,5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 8 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "8,0,4,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &times; 2",
      "answer": "30",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.6666...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 15 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "15,0,5,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{4}{7}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.571428571428...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{4}\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{3}{6}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &times; 3",
      "answer": "45",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 &times; 4",
      "answer": "84",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "16 &times; 6",
      "answer": "96",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; 6",
      "answer": "78",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "4&sup3;",
      "answer": "64",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{25}\\)",
      "answer": "5",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 4 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "4,0,2,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "3&sup2;",
      "answer": "9",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "8&sup2;",
      "answer": "64",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{10}{11}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.909090...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{5}{10}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the decimal expansion of \\(\\dfrac{7}{9}\\)?",
      "answer": "0.7777...",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"]
    },
    {
      "question": "17 &times; 2",
      "answer": "34",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "19 &times; 5",
      "answer": "95",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    }
  ]
}
